toshiba.co.uk 2018-11-26

# Privacy Policy - Toshiba

**Toshiba of Europe is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.**

This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website (the “Site”). We may revise this policy and would recommend that you check the current version and the date of issue, located at the base of this document.

 **Topics:**

  * Who are we?
  * What information do we about you?
  * How will we use the information about you?
  * Marketing
  * Access to your information and correction
  * Webserver data
  * Cookies
  * Your right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority
  * Other websites
  * Protection of children
  * Changes to our privacy policy
  * How to contact us

**Who are we?**

We are Toshiba of Europe Limited, part of the Toshiba Corporation and we operate across Europe under the laws of the United Kingdom, the location of our headquarters. Our company number is 03468211 and we are registered at 3 Furzeground Way, Stockley Park, Uxbridge, Middlesex, UB11 1EZ, United Kingdom.

Toshiba of Europe Limited is the data controller responsible for your personal information processed via the Site.

Toshiba of Europe Limited does not directly sell or offer any products, solutions or services to businesses or individuals across Europe. Toshiba’s individual divisions are separate businesses, and each has its own privacy policy which can be accessed via that division’s website.

 **What information do we collect about you?**

When you use this Site, Toshiba of Europe Limited collects statistical and usage information from your visit. Further details can be found within the Cookie policy and the Webserver data section of this document. Where your personal information is completely anonymised, we do not require a legal basis to use it as the information will no longer constitute personal information that is regulated under data protection laws.

We also collect personal information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback on our website and participate in competitions. Toshiba of Europe Limited does not currently run such activity and in any future event you will be provided full, specific terms of data collection at the point of submission. It is in our legitimate interest to use any future, personal information you provide in this way in such a way to ensure that we provide the very best services to you.

Toshiba of Europe Limited does collect website usage data via cookies. Further details on the specific cookies that are being used can be found within the Cookie policy document.

 **How will we use the information about you?**

Toshiba of Europe Limited does not collect any personal information about you on the Site other than usage data for analytical reasons, and we do not use this to identify any individual user. We do not store, have access to or use in any way personal information about you other than data related to your use of this Site.

As outlined, we will be collecting information about your activity on this website via cookies. Further details are in the Cookies section of this document.

 **Marketing**

As outlined, Toshiba of Europe Limited does not directly provide any products, solutions or services to either businesses or individuals across Europe. Because of this, we will not be contacting you or be performing any marketing activity which might directly target you.

If this website is used as part of any extended marketing activity for a Toshiba division, then information on any relevant cookies will be located within the Cookie policy. Further information on how to define the Google ad settings on your device can be found here: <http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads/>.

Additionally, Toshiba of Europe Limited does not directly perform or engage in any ‘retargeting’ or ‘remarketing’ activity, a technique which uses your online activity to customise offers, promotions or content for you on other websites. If this website is used as part of the remarketing activity for any Toshiba division, then information on any associated cookies will be found within the Cookie policy.

 **Access to your information and correction**

As outlined within this document, Toshiba of Europe Limited does not collect or store any identifiable personal information about any individual. If you have any concerns that Toshiba of Europe Limited is holding any information which might identify you, then you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. Further information about data rights is set out below.

To get in contact please email or write to us using the details found within our Corporate Information page. We may make a small charge for this service.

 **Webserver data**

When you visit the Site, as is usual on almost all websites, our server automatically collects information such as your IP address, the date and time of each visit to our website, how much data was processed and the pages visited on our website. We use this information to improve your website experience and do not use this information to identify you.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track usage of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.

Further information on the cookies deployed, how they’re used and their retention period can be found within the Cookie policy document.

 **Other websites**

The Site contains links to other websites, including Toshiba’s main corporation website and Toshiba division sites across Europe which are wholly owned and managed by those divisions. This privacy policy only applies to this website, so when you link to other websites you should read their specific privacy policies.

 **Protection of children**

The Site is not addressed to children and young people under the age of 16. Children and young people under the age of 16 may not transmit any personal data over the Internet without the consent of their parent or guardian. As outlined, Toshiba of Europe Limited does not currently request personal information from site users and does not store any personal data known to belong to children.

 **Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this Site. This privacy policy was last updated on 14.05.2018.

 **Your right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority.**

If you have a concern about any aspect of our privacy practices, you can report it to your local data protection regulator. The full list of local data protection authorities can be found at <http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080>

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or our commitment to protecting your data. Our contact details are located on our Corporate Information page.

Version number: v1.0  
Date of publication: 14.05.2018 

This document has been reviewed and revised in accordance with and prior to the introduction of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
